[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the pirate that the Goonies are searching for in the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "One-Eyed Willie", "incorrect_answers": ["Boot-strapped Billie", "One-Eyed Billie", "Boot-Strapped Willie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Adam Schiff, the Manhattan District Attorney in Law and Order?", "correct_answer": "Steven Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["Fred Dalton Thompson", "Dann Florek", "Steve Zirnkilton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1839, while spending the winter with George Sand in Majorca, this composer completed a work  consisting of 24 short preludes. Each prelude was in a different major or minor key.", "correct_answer": "Chopin", "incorrect_answers": ["Schubert", "Schumann", "Lizst"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Overconsumption of sugar causes hyperactivity in children, manifested by increased movement, impulsiveness, distractibility, and mood swings.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1944 film Arsenic and Old Lace, which is based on a play by Joseph Kesselring?", "correct_answer": "Frank Capra", "incorrect_answers": ["WIlford Jackson", "Alfred Hitchcock", "Charles Chaplin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the part of Sam Bowdens daughter in Cape Fear?", "correct_answer": "Juliette Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Drew Barymore", "Christina  Applegate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1994 we broke out our tissue boxes as we watched Andy Garcia struggle with his wifes (played by Meg Ryan) alcoholism in what film?", "correct_answer": "When A Man Loves A Woman", "incorrect_answers": ["Stand and Deliver", "Jennifer 8", "Desperate Measures"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Forrest Gump describes to Jenny all the beautiful scenes he saw while he was running across America. She said she wished she could have been there with him. What does Forrest say in response?", "correct_answer": "You were.", "incorrect_answers": ["Me too.", "But you dont like to run Jenny.", "Okay."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the translation of the term \u00c9tats g\u00e9n\u00e9raux which was used to refer to the French Parliament?", "correct_answer": "States General", "incorrect_answers": ["Military Generals", "General law-makers", "General Assembly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1997 sci-fi movie featured Agent K and former NYPD officer, Agent J?", "correct_answer": "Men in Black", "incorrect_answers": ["The Iron Giant", "Independence Day", "Titan A.E."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which man-made island, located to the southwest of Singapore, was created by joining several natural islands?", "correct_answer": "Jurong Island", "incorrect_answers": ["Formoza", "Spiral Island", "Neeltje-Jans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This ingredient is often used in anti-cellulite lotions and slim gels because it enhances the micro-circulation and easily dissolves body fat.", "correct_answer": "Caffeine", "incorrect_answers": ["Chocolate", "Nicotine", "THC"]}]